[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 15, "question": "Perfect, huh?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 16, "answer": "This is PIERS MORGAN TONIGHT.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "And anyone see this coming?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NN", "VB", "DT", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "No, certainly not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 48, "question": "So what are we to make of all this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 49, "answer": "Well, he is an actor.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Arnold"]}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "Where do you see Arnold Schwarzenegger's position here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "Well, Arnold is an interesting case because he does have sort of a larger-than-life persona on the screen.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Arnold Schwarzenegger"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "What are the projects that Arnold Schwarzenegger is currently considering?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "Well, there's a couple.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Arnold Schwarzenegger"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "So I think if she continues to not be publicly anti-him then I would imagine his movie career could be perfectly OK, couldn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "RB", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "RB", "NNP", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "From everything that you're hearing tonight of this offer that's come forward from Strauss-Kahn's attorneys, does it seem to be the kind of deal you would expect to be accepted, that he will be released on bail tomorrow?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "NN", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "POS", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "Well, I would think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Strauss-Kahn"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "Has he been treated any differently to anybody else would be treated in his position if they weren't well known?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "TO", "NN", "RB", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "No, he's treated equally poor that we treat everybody in our criminal justice system.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "But in terms of this guy, his reputation, he has an incredibly powerful job, if you take the presumption of innocent until proven guilty, it's pretty unfair, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "It's very unfair.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "Would you feel confident at this stage of defending this successfully?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "No, I would not feel confident.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "Edward Black, I mean, when you hear what Alan Dershowitz said there, do you agree with him in terms of the tactics?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "Not necessarily.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Edward Black"], "PERSON": ["Alan Dershowitz"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Eliot"]}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 185, "question": "Alan Dershowitz?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 186, "answer": "You know, Eliot --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "How are you, Piers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "I've been looking forward to this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "You're confident, are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "You think you're going to take me down?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "No, not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "UGENT: Boy, did they need me there, huh?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "And just to describe how you thought went with this British interview, you said they sent this young limey prick who pretended to be my friend.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mrs. Nugent"]}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "My point would be -- I mean do you ever accept you might be wrong?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "Mrs. Nugent is here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 259, "question": "What was your view of America right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 260, "answer": "My view of America right now is so beautiful I can hardly stand myself.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "JJR", "CC", "JJR", "NN", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", ",", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "What don't you like about America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "I don't like about America is what is being celebrated in politics, where instead of being the best that you can be, we seem to be engineering more and more safety nets, which creates, encourages and rewards an uncaring disconnect.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "What do you mean safety nets?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "Well, safety nets.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 285, "question": "Have you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "And I admire --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "That doesn't mean to say that they are any less susceptible to being corrupt when it comes to welfare than anybody else, does it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "TO", "VBG", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "No, not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "Do you regret that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "You know, I do regret it on one level.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "Is part of that a guilt thing on your part?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "No, not a guilt thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 352, "question": "Would you bring that up if I'd been clean and sober for 50 years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "Probably, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 361, "question": "How's this, Piers, when I graduated -- how old are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 362, "answer": "I'm 46.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "U.S."]}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NNP", "NNS", "JJR", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "And that's -- can I just come about once more to the motivation for why you now do so much stuff?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", ":", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "JJR", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "Because I've learned that freedom is not free and I found that the reason the whole world sucks and America sucks less is because the U.S. Constitution, the Bill of Rights, outlines an experiment where freedom rules the day of individuality and that that can only be secured by crushing those enemies that would take it away.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "If you have the time again I suspect now the Ted Nugent you've become, you'd go to Vietnam, wouldn't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "NNP", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "Damn right I would.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ted Nugent"], "LOCATION": ["Vietnam"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 404, "question": "So that would be in your eyes the biggest mistake of your life, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "No, because --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "Is there any nobler sacrifice?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "There is no nobler sacrifice.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "You ready to roll?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "You bet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "Did you enjoy that or didn't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CC", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "ORGAN: No, I'm amused by your reaction.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 445, "question": "Well, let me put it in official CNN Piers Morgan interview terms, shall I?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "NNS", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CNN Piers Morgan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "Why do you guys resist that statistic?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "Well, don't say you guys.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "If you had your way, there would be 10 times as many firearms, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "EX", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "Not true at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "You want everyone in America to own a gun?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "Not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "What is your position?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "-- and I hope you don't edit this out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "What does Nugent want?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "NNP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "Not even close.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nugent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 500, "question": "What do you want?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 501, "answer": "What I want is the Second Amendment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "How could he be allowed to get a gun?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "Because he fell through the cracks, and he didn't -- he didn't qualify to get a gun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "How would you fix that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "Well, I would certainly make it a lot harder for people like him to ever get near a firearm.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["England"]}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "Were you born in England?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "I was born in England.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["England"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "Are you familiar with Ireland?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Ireland"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 528, "question": "Is Molotov cocktails and C4 explosives -- those legal in Belfast?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "NNS", "CC", "NNP", "NNS", ":", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 529, "answer": "They're terrorists.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Belfast"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Belfast"]}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "Are those -- is that -- are those items legal in Belfast?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", ":", "VBZ", "IN", ":", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "Well, I don't live in Belfast.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Belfast"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "Would you agree drugs then to be freely available?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "RB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "Not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "VBP", "CD", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBG", "JJ", ",", "VBG", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "ORGAN: What's the difference in the argument?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "Because drugs are 100 percent about reducing your level of responsibility, getting high, disconnecting, and I'm a cop.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "EX", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "My point about the threat of your argument is you're saying -- there's a difference, isn't there, between -- you're saying guns should be made freely available, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "No, no, there should be restrictions.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FBI"]}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "And you don't believe that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "Not only do I -- the FBI doesn't believe it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "Now that you know that, why wouldn't you help me create more safe areas?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "We'll have a break.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "From what I can read, she's the only one you have any time for in the GOP, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["GOP"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 598, "question": "Mitt Romney, your thoughts?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 599, "answer": "A good man.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 613, "question": "Did you agree with him about the birther issue?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 614, "answer": "You know, I agree that we should be able to demand evidence and I, like he and many others, I had not seen the official document.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 616, "question": "Have you seen Sarah Palin's?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "."], "aSentId": 617, "answer": "I have not seen -- but she's not president.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarah Palin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 618, "question": "Why aren't you demanding to see hers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 619, "answer": "If she runs for president I would.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 626, "question": "Have you ever asked to see the birth certificate of any other president or presidential candidate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 627, "answer": "No, I haven't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 628, "question": "Why not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "I was never active enough in politics --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 631, "question": "Because the question came up whether he -- here's what I would expect, Piers, and I think -- are you an American citizen now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "PRP", ":", "RB", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 632, "answer": "Not yet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", ":", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 648, "question": "If you're so determined to get these questions answered, when are you going to start asking where Sarah Palin's birth certificate is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 649, "answer": "The minute she -- the minute she runs for president.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarah Palin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 650, "question": "You will?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 651, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 662, "question": "Were you born here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 663, "answer": "Hopelessly, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "EX", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 669, "question": "Newt Gingrich?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 670, "answer": "Probably the smartest guy out there and when he speaks, he speaks for me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 671, "question": "Would you vote for him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 672, "answer": "Right now, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 674, "question": "Tim Pawlenty?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 675, "answer": "A great man.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tim Pawlenty"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 681, "question": "Why are you such a big fan of Sarah Palin?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 682, "answer": "Because it's quintessential American politics.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarah Palin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 697, "question": "You're quite keen on that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 698, "answer": "Yes, I'm keen on that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 738, "question": "Are you homophobic?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 739, "answer": "Not at all, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "NNS", ":", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 742, "question": "What's a heterophiliac?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 743, "answer": "It means I'm hopelessly addicted to women -- woman.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 746, "question": "How would you react to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 747, "answer": "UGENT: I'd say, get the gun, let's go kill a dear.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 749, "question": "You wouldn't mind morally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 750, "answer": "Not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 787, "question": "What is a quaint old thing where if there aren't any guns nobody gets shot?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 788, "answer": "And if there isn't any water, no one will drown.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 806, "question": "Why would you ban water?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 807, "answer": "To stop the drownings.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 837, "question": "Piers Morgan, sing this with me, would you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "PRP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 838, "answer": "A fascinating encounter.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Morgan"]}}]